[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "I don't -- really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "And while he tries to form the question, I'll tell you who's with me tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Not at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I went to a Jewish high school, gloom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["McKinley High"]}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Yes, the teachers say, yes, you can sing, but you're Jewish, go to work, learn, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "We don't have any Jews at McKinley High.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "I love how you say I looked down and there was a great bunny slipper and you say, why -- why is my bunny slippers so gray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Right, right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Did you pay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Do we understand each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robin Williams"]}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 200, "question": "And you look at Robin Williams, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Robin Williams is --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robin Williams"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "What's so terrible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Yes, I say actress, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "So are you into politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Why do you hate it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "First of all, the joke is, the Obamas are the white person -- people now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Didn't you say in your movie Jack Lemon walked out once?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Lemon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "One of your first roles you played a lesbian in the '50s in a play and you're in love with Barbra Streisand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "''", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 391, "question": "This is -- yes, pre-\"Funny Girl,\" right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "''", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Pre-\"Funny Girl.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "The two of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "IVERS: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Was that great?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Yes, that was -- she went through the gift thing and like took everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "And you kissed her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Smack on the lips.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Isn't that something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "If I was to use her, who's going to watch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I have done a lot of understudying where you're kind of -- you're kind of get there in the right place at the right time kind of accidentally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "What do you want?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "I will take anything, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "That's because you love the craft.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["West Bank"]}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 557, "question": "You still do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I work at the West Bank --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "You look great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Does it hurt your feelings, too?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "It affects your self-esteem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Totally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "What self-esteem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "-NONE-", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Do you have a twin brother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "See?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "And you do it yourself or do you have someone come over?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "On important days I have someone comes over.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joan", "Melissa Rivers"]}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Is it yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Well, Joan, coming up soon, we're going to be speaking of is this yours, Melissa Rivers, yours --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "What kinds of conduct, verbal conduct might be problematic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Once I had a boss come in and say oh, I had a sex dream about you last night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "Who was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I'm not telling you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Was it Oprah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "The point was --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "YNCH: How does it make you feel to know that everybody witnessed that humiliation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "I didn't really have a choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Are you as compelled as your mother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I don't know any other way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 819, "question": "That date book of yours is full now, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 820, "answer": "I call mine the career.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "How many times?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "That's a good one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 887, "question": "Have you been in love after?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 888, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 889, "question": "Could you keep that to yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 890, "answer": "-- your father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", ":", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 897, "question": "How long were you together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 898, "answer": "We were together until -- about 10 and a half years and then he cheated on me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 899, "question": "That was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 900, "answer": "At that age, an old guy --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 905, "question": "Have you ever been in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 906, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "Were you in love with your ex-husband?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "When we met, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 921, "question": "Is he an active father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 922, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 983, "question": "What do you think is going to go down for the Republicans in this primary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 984, "answer": "Well, he who predicts -- he who looks into the crystal ball in this cycle ends up eating glass, as we say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1013, "question": "Do you think that if he becomes the nominee -- and it looks like he probably will -- that the party will be able to unify around him, that there will be some energy and some wind at his back coming into the general election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1014, "answer": "First, let me say, I never had grits until I moved down here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1082, "question": "Is that true, Mary Matalin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1083, "answer": "Yes, we call it a cosmetology license, and I'm very good.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Matalin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1132, "question": "How does it feel to be the most famous person in Grand Forks, North Dakota?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1133, "answer": "Well, it's -- obviously it's overwhelming, it's wild, crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Grand Forks", "North Dakota"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1158, "question": "Maybe in the summer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1159, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1162, "question": "What was your response?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1163, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1193, "question": "Have you ever been to an Olive Garden?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1194, "answer": "I sure have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]